<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClientRegister</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="tc_title">WORK HEALTH AND SAFETY POLICY</string>
    <string name="tc_content">Obligations
Management is firmly committed to a policy enabling all work activities to be carried out safely, and with all possible measures taken to remove(or at least reduce) risks to the health, safety and welfare or workers, contractors, authorizsed visitors, and anyone else who may be affected by our operations.\n
We are committed to ensuring we comply with the Work Health and Safety Act 2012, the Work Health and Safety Regulations 2012 and applicable Codes of Practice and Australian Standards as far as possible.\n
Responsibilities\n
-  Management:\n
Will provide and maintain as far as possible:\n
•  a safe working environment\n
•  safe systems of work\n
•  plant and substances in safe condition\n
•  facilities for the welfare of workers\n
•  information, instruction, training and supervision that is reasonably nessary to ensure  that each worker is safe from injury and risks to health\n
•  a commitment to consult and co-operate with workers in all matters relating to health and safety in the workplace\n
•  a commitment to continually improve our performance through effective safety management.\n
-  Workers:\n
Each worker has an obligation to:\n
•  comply with safe work practices, with the intent of avoiding injury to themselves and others and damage to plant and equipment\n
•  take reasonable care of the health and safety of themselves and others\n
•  wear personal protective equipment and clothing where necessary\n
•  comply with any direction given by management for health and safety\n
•  not misuse or interfere with anything provided for health and safety\n
•  report all accidents and incidents on the job immediately, no mattter how trivial\n
•  report all known or observed hazards to their supervisor or manager.\n
Application of this policy\n
We seek the co-operation of all workers, customers and other persons. We encourage suggestions for realising our health and safety objectives to create a safe working environment with a zero accident rate.\n
-  Goals\n
This Policy:\n
•  shows the commitment of (your business name)'s management and workers to health and safety\n
•  aims to remove or reduce the risks to the health, safety and welfare of all workers, contractors and visitors, and anyone else who may be affected by our business operations\n
•  aims to ensure all work activities are done safely.\n
-  Responsibilities\n
Management (the supervisor and / or manager) is responsible for providing and maintaining:\n
•  a safe working environment\n
•  safe systems of work\n
•  plant and substances in a safe condition\n
•  facilities for the welfare of all workers\n
•  any information, instruction, training and supervision needed to make sure that all workers are safe from injury and risks to their health\n
•  [LIST ANY OTHER SPECIFIC HEALTH AND SAFETY DUTIES THAT MANAGEMENT HAS].\n
Workers are responsible for:\n
•  ensuring their own personal health and safety, and that of others in the workplace\n
•  complying with any reasonable directions (such as safe work procedures, wearing personal protective equipment) given by management for health ad safety\n
•  [LIST ANY OTHER SPECIFIC HEALTH AND SAFETY DUTIES THAT MANAGEMENT HAS].\n
We expect visitors and contractors to:\n
• [INCLUDE HOW YOU WANT THESE PEOPLE TO COMPLY WITH THIS POLICY AND THE PROCEDURES YOU HAVE THAT ENSURE HEALTH AND SAFETY AT YOUR WORKPLACE]\n</string>
</resources>
